# Bassel A.M. Qadah

Ramallah,Palestine |009725403692| bqqadah@gmail.com https://sites.google.com/view/myresume2024

## **Objective**

A Human who cares for continuity and has excellent skills in time management and learning quickly with a passion for storytelling as part of a product team, keen to gain practical experience in the international NGO sector and contribute to intercultural understanding.

#### Education

#### • Birzeit University

Bachelor's degree in electrical engineering

2020 - present

## **Experience**

## • Wikipedia Editor

Wikipedia Palestine

2023 - Present

- Conducted thorough research to write factual and informative content for Wikipedia articles, ensuring accuracy and adherence to Wikipedia's Manual of Style.
- Verified information through credible sources to maintain the integrity of Wikipedia's content.
- Collaborated with other editors to discuss edits, address discrepancies, and reach consensus.

## **Training Courses**

- Enriching Arabic Content on Wikipedia 20 training hours
- CNC Carpentry Systems 18 training hours
- Design Trainee (2024 Present) 3 training hours
- Montage: Technical & Creative Vision
- Graphic Design in coursera
- A special course on the hashtag Palestine
- Work Smarter, Not Harder: Time Management for Personal & Professional Productivity in <u>coursera</u>
- Innovar in coursera
- Adobe Lightroom CC Photo Editing in udemy
- Student Parliament Coordinator Trainee (2016-2018)
- electrical technician

#### **Skills**

- Content Production and Editing
- Good cross-cultural understanding and communication
- Teamwork
- Effective Time Management
- Social Media Management
- Interest in ancient Arts and Culture
- Communication Skills

## Language Skills

- Arabic Speaking and Writing (native language)
- English Speaking and Writing (Good)
- Turkish (Good)

#### volunteering

- Cooperative Work Activities Western Entrance Cleaning Projects
- Collaborative Work Activities Cleaning & Painting
- Collaborative Work Activities Wiki Palestine Projects
- Collaborative Work Activities Cleaning & Painting
- International Women's Day Edit-a-thon
- Love Gesture Initiative
- Internal Initiative Leadership and Active Citizenship
- Internal Debate Station Leadership and Active Citizenship
- Coordinator at the Student Parliament

#### References

Batoul Qaisia

Project coordinator

wikipalestine@gmail.com

Ghada Al-Omari

Cooperative Work Program Coordinator - Deanship of Student Affairs gomare@birzeit.edu